A Guide to the Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JHPI) records FA476
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Files and Grants, 1
  - Mount Rainier National Park- Report on Survey of Need for and Economic Feasibility of Hotel Facilities in Mt. Rainier National Park (Final Copy), 1959 (Box 34)
    Scope and Contents note
    Final Copy
  - Mount Rainier National Park- Report (Preliminary Report on Survey of Need for Economic Feasibility of Hotel Facilities), 1959 (Box 34)
    Extra Copies.
  - Mount Rainier National Park - General, 1959 (Box 35)
  - Mount Rainier National Park - General, 1958 (Box 35)
  - Mount Rainier National Park - General, 1957 (Box 35)
  - Mount Rainier National Park - Copies of study (Box 35)
  - Mount Rainier National Park - Architect's Study - Spencer and Lee (Box 35)
  - Mount Rainier National Park - Architect's Study - Spencer and Lee (Box 35)
    Extra copies.
  - Mount Rainier National Park - Archltect's Study - Spencer and Lee (Box 35)
    Final copies.
  - Mount Rainier National Park - Booklets (Picture Story) (Box 35)
  - Mount Rainier National Park - Booklets (Picture Story) (Box 35)
  - National Park Service - Great Sierra Mine Cabin on Tioga Hill and Mona Pass (Box 35)
  - National Park Service - Mission 66 Program (Box 35)
  - National Park Service - Wawona Bridge (Yosemite Park) (Box 35)
  - National Park Service - General Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 35)
  - National Park Service - General Correspondence, 1958 (Box 35)
  - National Park Service - General Correspondence, 1957 (Box 35)
  - National Park Service - General Correspondence, 1956 (Box 35)
  - National Park Service, 1955 (Box 35)
  - National Park Service, 1954 (Box 35)
  - National Park Service, 1953 (Box 35)
  - National Park Service, 1952 (Box 35)
  - National Park Service, 1951 (Box 35)
  - National Park Service, 1950 (Box 35)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - National Park Service - Water Rights, 1951 (Box 35)
  - Osborn, F., 1951-1955 (Box 35)
  - Photographs, 1950 (Box 35)
  - Property Purchase - Gabbey, 1947 (Box 36)
  - Property Purchase - Rams Hom Ranch, 1950 (Box 36)
  - Property Purchase - Schwabacher, 1951 (Box 36)
  - Property Purchase - White Grass Ranch, 1949 (Box 36)
  - President's Fishlng Trip, 1955 (Box 36)
  - Property Purchase - (A-H) by name, 1950 (Box 36)
  - Property Purchase - (I-Z) by name, 1950 (Box 36)
  - Property Purchase - Brinkerhoff, 1955 (Box 36)
  - Property Purchase - Barker, Circle H Ranch, 1950 (Box 36)
  - Property Purchase - Corse, 1953 (Box 36)
  - Property Purchase - Craighead, 1951 (Box 36)
  - Property Purchase - Doran, 1946 (Box 36)
  - Property Purchase - Gordon, 1954 (Box 36)
  - Property Purchase - Gray, 1947 (Box 36)
  - Property Purchase - Jenkins, 1947 (Box 36)
  - Property Purchase - Hunter, 1952 (Box 36)
  - Property Purchase - Mormon Row, 1949 (Box 36)
  - Property Purchase - R Lazy S Ranch, 1951 (Box 36)
  - Property Purchase - (by name), 1955 (Box 36)
  - Jackson Hole Promotion (Box 36)
  - Publicity, 1952-1953 (Box 36)
  - Publicity, 1950-1951 (Box 36)
  - Resor, S., 1950 (Box 36)
  - Roads, 1952-1953 (Box 36)
  - Roads, 1950-1951 (Box 36)
  - Rockefeller Family - Portraits, 1944-1945 (Box 36)
  - A (Box 36)
  - Rockefeller, John D. Jr., 1959 (Box 36)
  - Rockefeller, John D. Jr., 1954-1955 (Box 36)
  - Rockefeller, John D. Jr., 1952-1953 (Box 36)
  - Rockefeller, John D. Jr., 1950-1951 (Box 36)
  - Rockefeller, John D. Jr. - Files, 1952-1954 (Box 36)
  - Rockefeller, John D. Jr. - Jackson Hole, 1943-1949 (Box 36)
  - Rockefeller, John D. Jr. - Duplicates, 1954 (Box 36)
  - Rockefeller, John D. Jr. - Duplicates, 1952-1953 (Box 36)
  - WMSBG - Rockefeller, John D. Jr. - Special Folder - Strictly Confidential (Box 36)
  - Rockefeller, John D. Jr. - Duplicates, 1950-1951 (Box 36)
  - Rockefeller, John D. Jr. - Tilden Book (Box 36)
  - Rockefeller, Mrs. John D. Jr. (Box 36)
  - JDR Jr.- Bracbman Portrait- 1941-1944 (Box 36)
  - JDR Jr.- Bracbman Portrait- 1940 (Box 36)
  - JDR Jr.- Portraits- 1941-1944 (Box 36)
  - JDR Jr.- "The Creed" (Box 36)
  - Fosdick, Raymond - Book - JDR Jr., 1955 (Box 36)
  - Rockefeller, John D. Jr. - Fosdick Biography, 1952-1954 (Box 36)
  - John D. Rockefeller Jr. - Book by Raymond Fosdick, 1956 (Box 36)
  - Rockefeller, John D. Jr. (Death of) - General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 37)
  - Rockefeller, John D. Jr. (Death of)- Individuals (A-Z), 1960 (Box 37)
  - Rockefeller, John D. Jr. Will and Testament - Confidential, 1960 (Box 37)
  - Rockefeller, John D. 3rd, 1949 (Box 37)
  - Rockefeller, David, 1952 (Box 37)
  - Rockefeller, David, 1957 (Box 37)
  - South Calaveras Grove, 1954 (Box 37)
  - South Calaveras- 1952 (Box 37)
  - Rockefeller, Winthrop, 1957-1961 (Box 37)
  - Rockefeller, Winthrop (Mrs.) (Box 37)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson, 1957 (Box 37)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance, 1950-1952 (Box 37)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance, 1953-1954 (Box 37)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson (Box 37)
  - Rockefeller Center - "Last Rivet", 1940 (Box 37)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1948-1955 (Box 37)
  - School Lands, 1953 (Box 37)
  - Schwabacher, A., 1951 (Box 37)
  - Simpson, M., 1953 (Box 37)
  - Skinner, D., 1952 (Box 37)
  - Solicitations & Donations (Box 37)
  - Speeches- Rockefeller, Laurance S. - "People and Parks" (Superintendents Meeting), 1957 September 17 (Box 37)
  - South Pass City, 1953 (Box 37)
  - Square G Ranch, 1952 (Box 37)
  - St. John's Hospital, 1955 (Box 37)
  - Wort, Jess, 1953 (Box 37)
  - K.C. Personal - Fairmount Park Art Association, 1959 (Box 37)
  - Taxes, 1950 (Box 37)
  - Tours, 1950 (Box 37)
  - Tresidder, D., 1942 (Box 37)
  - Webb, V., 1950 (Box 37)
  - Webb, V., 1953-1954 (Box 37)
  - Yellowstone Park Co., 1953 (Box 37)
  - Albright, Horace (Testimonial Dinner) - General Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 38)
  - Albright, Horace (Testimonial Dinner) - General Correspondence (Box 38)
  - Albright, Horace (Testimonial Dinner) Temp. Folder, Individuals (A-L), 1959 (Box 38)
  - Albright, Horace (Testimonial Dinner) Temp. Folder, Individuals (M-Z) (Box 38)
  - Albright, Horace (Testimonial Dinner) - Cards, 1950 (Box 38)
  - Albright, Horace (Luncheon- Stag), 1960 January (Box 38)
  - Albright, Horace (Testimonial Dinner) - Meetings (Box 38)
  - Albright, Horace (Testimonial Dinner) - Samples (tickets, programs, etc.) and Drafts, News Release (Box 38)
  - Albright, Horace (Testimonial Dinner) - Clippings, etc., 1959 (Box 38)
  - Albright, Horace (Testimonial Dinner Photos), 2 folders. (Box 38)
  - Binder List of Person's and Their Contributions (Box 38)
  - Bassett Hall, 1960 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall, 1956-1959 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall, 1955 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall, 1950 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall, 1949-1952 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall, 1947-1948 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall, 1941-1944 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall, 1937-1940 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall, 1936 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall, 1931-1935 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall, 1928-1930 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall - Dam, 1941-1944 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall - Estate & Homestead, 1941-1944 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall Incorporated, 1941-1942 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall Incorporated, 1940 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall Incorporated, 1938-1939 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall Landscaping, 1942-1944 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall Landscaping, 1940-1941 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall Landscaping, 1938-1939 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall Landscaping, 1936-1937 (Box 39)
  - Bassett Hall Landscaping, 1929-1934 (Box 39)
  - Properties - JDR Jr. - General, 1956 (Box 39)
  - Properties- JDR Jr.- Individuals A-Z, 1956 (Box 39)
  - Properties - Rockefeller, JDR Jr., 1955 (Box 39)
  - Properties - Rockefeller, JDR Jr., 1954 (Box 39)
  - Properties - Rockefeller, JDR Jr., 1953 (Box 39)
  - Properties - Rockefeller, JDR Jr., 1952 (Box 39)
  - Properties - Rockefeller, JDR Jr., 1950-1951 (Box 39)
  - PreliminarySurveyofYellowstoneParkCompany, 19 copies. (Box 40)
  - Preliminary Survey of Yellowstone Park Company, 4 copies. (Box 41)
  - App. A - Background: Yellowstone Park (Box 41)
  - App. B - Background: Major Yellowstone Park Concessions (Box 41)
  - App. C - Background: Yellowstone Park Company (Box 41)
  - App. D - Facilities and Services (Box 41)
  - App. E - Organization: General Management (Box 41)
  - App. F - Organization: Operating, 1965 (Box 41)
  - App. G - Relations with National Park Service and Other Concessioners: Contracts (Box 41)
  - App. H - Relations with Nation Park Service and Other Concessioners: Proposed Legislation and Congressional Reports (Box 41)
  - App. I - Relations with NPS and other Concessioners: Miscellaneous (Box 41)
  - App. J - Operating Practices and Results and Financial Position (Box 41)
  - App. K - Market Potential (Box 41)
  - App. L - Relations with National Park Service (Box 41)
  - App. M - Facilities Development Program (Box 41)
  - App. N - Conclusion (Box 41)
  - Angel Island (Proposal) - San Francisco Bay (Box 42)
  - Conservation Projects- Individual (A-Z) (Box 42)
  - Directors (Prospective) Individuals (A-Z) (Box 42)
  - Finance - Gifts to JHPI, 1958 (Box 42)
  - Finance - Gifts to JHPI, 1957 (Box 42)
  - Finance - Gifts to JHPI, 1956 (Box 42)
  - Finance - Investments, 1960 (Box 42)
  - Finance - Investments, 1959 (Box 42)
  - Grosvenor, Melville B. (Box 42)
  - Mapes Cabin (Snug Harbor) (Box 42)
  - Committee Meeting Agendas (Box 42)
  - Meetings - Transportation, 1963 (Box 42)
  - Meetings - Transportation, 1961 (Box 42)
  - Meetings - Transportation, 1960 (Box 42)
  - National Foundation for Junior Museums (Box 42)
  - National Park Service - Employees and Alumni Association (Box 42)
  - National Park Service - High Sierra Camps and GTNP Camps (Report) (Box 42)
  - National Park Service "Nation Park Wilderness" (Booklet) (Box 42)
  - National Park Service State Parks Manual (Box 42)
  - Ordway, Samuel H. (Box 42)
  - Romney, Henry (Director) (Box 42)
  - Palisades Interstate Park Commission (Rockland Lake Project) (Box 42)
  - Wildhorse Island (Box 42)
  - JHPI- Yosemite National Park- Minarets Project (Box 42)
  - K.C. Personal - Batsto Citizen's Committee, 1960 (Box 42)
  - Report - Historical Aspects of the Wharton Tract (Box 42)
  - K.C. Personal - Batsto Citizen's Committee, 1958 (Box 42)
  - K.C. Personal - Batsto Citizen's Committee, 1957 (Box 42)
  - K.C. Personal - Batsto Citizen's Committee, 1961 (Box 42)
  - K.C. Personal - Church of the Transfiguration (Gantner, Carl) (Box 43)
  - Conservation - Clippings, Booklets, etc. (Box 43)
  - Conservation Book - "Contribution to the Heritage of Every American" - Distribution - General (Box 43)
  - Conservation Book - "Contribution to the Heritage of Every American" - Distribution - Individuals (A-Z) (Box 43)
    Including Acknowledgements
  - Conservation Book- "Contribution to the Heritage of Every American" Text (Box 43)
  - Conservation Book - "Thank You Letters" - (R.L. Hoke) (Box 43)
  - Conservation Book - "Contribution to the Heritage of Every American" - General Correspondence, 1957 (Box 43)
  - Conservation Book - "Contribution to the Heritage of Every American" - General Correspondence, 1956 (Box 43)
  - Conservation Book - "Contribution to the Heritage of Every American" - General Correspondence, 1955 (Box 43)
  - Conservation Book - "Contribution to the Heritage of Every American" - Financial Aspects (Box 43)
  - Conservation Book (Box 43)
  - Contracts - Clerk, Frederick (Road Construction) (Box 43)
  - Contracts - Deed of Gift - Stark, Gustave Property (Parcel No. 52-A) (Box 43)
  - Contributions - General Summary (Box 43)
  - Contributions - Gifts Received (Box 43)
  - Contracts - Deed of Gift - Estate - Caneel Bay Parcel 12A (Little Cruz Bay) (Box 43)
  - Contract - Gift of Deed - St. John Virgin Island, 1956 (Box 43)
  - Dudley, Hoffman & McGowan (Box 43)
  - Finance - Annual Report of Board of Trustees (Annual Report ofTreasurer), 1962 (Box 43)
  - Finance - Annual Report of Treasurer - General Correspondence (Box 43)
  - Finance - Gifts to JHPI, 1959-1962 (Box 44)
  - First World Conference on Nation Parks (Seattle), 1962 (Box 44)
  - Glauser, Gertrude (Box 44)
  - Insurance - Self Insurance Plans (Box 44)
    Restricted from scholarly access - personnel material.
  - Insurance - Self Insurance Plans - Copies of Plans (Box 44)
  - Insurance - Workmen's Compensation (Box 44)
  - Annual Meeting, 1967 (Box 44)
  - Annual Meeting - Transportation, 1967 (Box 44)
  - Mount Rainier - General, 1960-1961 (Box 44)
  - National Park Service - General Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 44)
  - National Park Service - Acadia National Park (Box 44)
  - National Park Service - Acadia National Park - Mount Desert Study (Box 44)
  - National Park Service - "Financing Visitor Accommodation Services in National Park" (Box 44)
  - National Park Service - National Conference on State Parks (Box 44)
  - National Park Service - State Parks Book - Tilden (Box 44)
  - New York Disability Benefits Law (JDR Jr. Estate) (Box 44)
  - Newsom Earl & Company (Box 44)
  - Organization - General (Box 44)
  - Organization - Change of Name & Purpose (Box 44)
  - Organization - Officers - Resignation (Box 44)
  - Patterson, Belknap & Webb (Box 44)
  - Personnel - Employed - Branscombe, Jean M. (Box 44)
  - Personnel - Employed - Chorley K. (Box 44)
  - Pledges - Rockefeller, John D. Jr. (Box 44)
  - Power Launch Sale (Caneel Bay Plantation) (Box 44)
  - Publications, General (Box 44)
  - Report of Utah State Park and Recreation Commission - Kenneth Chorley, 1959 (Box 44)
  - Report of Utah State Park and Recreation Commission - Mildred Layne, 1959 (Box 44)
  - Reports - Employer - Management Improper Practices Act (Box 45)
  - Reports - Employer's Identification Number (Box 45)
  - Reports - (State of) New York - Dept. of Labor (NY Minimum Wage Act) (Box 45)
  - Reports - New York State Unemployment Insurance Law (Department of Labor) (Box 45)
  - Annual Report (Box 45)
  - Rockefeller Center Luncheon Club (Box 45)
    Expense Accounts of All Executives starting 1962 May.
  - Rockefeller, John D. (Jr.) (Box 45)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S., 1961-1962 (Box 45)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - thru 1960 (Box 45)
  - Reports - Newsom Earl & Co. (Box 45)
  - Rockefeller, Steven C. (Box 45)
    Restricted from scholarly access. Records which document the activities of living members of the Rockefeller family are restricted.
  - Save the Redwoods League, 1966 (Box 45)
  - Save the Redwoods League, 1965 (Box 45)
  - Save the Redwoods League, 1964 (Box 45)
  - Save the Redwoods League, 1963 (Box 45)
  - Save the Redwoods League, 1962 (Box 45)
  - Save the Redwoods League, 1961 (Box 45)
  - Wharton Tract, New Jersey (Box 45)
  - Caneel - Nation Park Service - Architectural Study Plan (Fisker, Professor Kay) (Box 45)
  - Annual Meeting, 1966 (Box 46)
  - Annual Meeting, 1965 (Box 46)
  - Meetings - Transportation, 1965 (Box 46)
  - Annual Meeting, 1964 (Box 46)
  - Annual Meeting, 1963 (Box 46)
  - Annual Meeting, 1962 (Box 46)
  - Meetings- Executive Committee, 1967 (Box 46)
  - Meetings - Executive, 1966 (Box 46)
  - Meetings - General, 1962-1965 (Box 46)
  - Meetings- Kenneth Chorley (Box 46)
  - Meetings - Board Meetings, 1960 October 29 (Box 46)
  - Organization By- Laws (Box 47)
  - Organization - Certificate of Incorporation (Box 47)
  - General Correspondence (Box 47)
  - Agreement - Note (Boulon, Ralf Hartwell) (Box 47)
  - Albright, Horace (Box 47)
  - American Conservation Association (Box 47)
  - Annual Reports (Box 47)
  - Applicants (Box 47)
  - Board of Trustees (Box 47)
  - Boats (Box 47)
  - British Virgin Islands (Government of) (Box 47)
  - British Virgin Islands (Government of) - Qualifying to do Business (Box 47)
  - British Virgin Islands (Government of) - Sage Mountain Rain Forest (Box 47)
  - College of the Virgin Islands Caribbean Research Institute - Virgin Islands Ecological Research Station, 1966 July (Box 47)
  - College of the Virgin Islands Caribbean Research Institute - Virgin Islands Ecological Research Station, 1965 August-1966 June (Box 47)
  - College of the Virgin Islands Caribbean Research Institute - Virgin Islands Ecological Research Station - Maps (Box 47)
  - College of the Virgin Islands Caribbean Research Institute - Virgin Islands Ecological Research Station - Printed Material (Box 47)
  - Contracts - Henley Cay Lease, 1958 (Box 47)
  - Contributions (Box 47)
  - Fabian, Harold P., 1959-1962 (Box 47)
  - Insurance - Group Travel (Box 48)
    Restricted from scholarly access.
  - Insurance - Employees (Box 48)
  - Harlem River Properties - Seekonk (Box 48)
  - Hudson Highlands Property Purchases (Box 48)
  - Hudson Highlands Property Purchases (Box 48)
  - Hudson Highlands Property Purchases (Box 48)
  - Hudson Highlands Property Purchase - Little Stony Point (Box 48)
  - Lease (Box 48)
  - Legal (Box 48)
  - Finance - General (Box 48)
  - Annual Statutory Report (Box 48)
  - Finances - Audits (Box 48)
  - Finance- Gifts to JHPI (Box 48)
  - Finance - Loans - General (Box 48)
  - Five Year Program (Box 48)
  - Five Year Program - Kenneth Chorley (Box 48)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of New York (Box 48)
  - Miller, Leslie A. (Box 49)
  - Annual Meeting, 1971 (Box 49)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1971 (Box 49)
  - Annual Meeting, 1970 (Box 49)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1970 (Box 49)
  - Annual Meeting, 1969 (Box 49)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1969 (Box 49)
  - Annual Meeting, 1968 (Box 49)
  - Annual Meeting - (Transportation), 1968 (Box 49)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1968 (Box 49)
  - Office Equipment (Box 49)
  - Office Furniture, Sale Of (Box 49)
  - Office Matters (Box 49)
  - Public Relations (Box 49)
  - Real Estate - Virgin Islands, St. John (Box 49)
  - Requests A-M (Box 49)
  - Requests N-Z (Box 49)
  - Rockefeller Brother's Fund (Box 49)
  - Rockefeller Brother Inc. (Including reports re. Dorado and Squaw Valley) (Box 49)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. (Box 49)
  - St. John's Hospital, Jackson, Wyoming (Box 50)
  - Save the Redwoods League (Box 50)
  - Save the Redwoods League, 1967 (Box 50)
  - Save the Redwoods League Inc. - Clippings (Box 50)
  - Taxes - General (Box 50)
  - Ruling Request, 1969 October 15 (Box 50)
  - Taxes - Federal - General Correspondence (Box 50)
  - Taxes - Deductibility (Box 50)
  - Taxes - Federal - Tax Exemption - Status Inquiry (Box 50)
  - Taxes - Federal - Tax Exemption - Status Inquiry #2 (Box 50)
  - Taxes - Federal - Tax Exemption Corporation Letter, 1942 (Box 50)
  - Proposed Registration Statement, 1967 (Box 50)
  - Taxes - State - Wyoming (Annual License Tax Form) (Box 50)
  - USG Dept. of the Interior - NPS - Grand Teton National Park Museum of the American Indian (Box 51)
  - USG Department of the Interior - NPS - Grand Teton National Park Museum of the American Indian (Box 51)
  - USG Department of the Interior - NPS - Grand Teton National Park Museum of the American Indian (Box 51)
  - USG Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service (Box 51)
  - USG Dept. of the Interior - NPS - Grand Teton National Park (Box 51)
  - USG Dept. of the Interior - NPS - National Park Concessions Inc. (Box 51)
  - USG Dept. of the Interior - NPS - Land Acquisitions - Matching Funds (Box 51)
  - National Park Service - Grand Teton National Park - Columbia University- Oral History (Box 51)
  - Indian Arts Museum, Colter Bay, Grand Teton National Park (Box 51)
  - USG Dept. of the Interior - NPS - Grand Teton National Park Museum of the American Indian - Printed Material (Box 51)
  - Miscellaneous Folder (Box 51)
  - USG Dept. of the Interior - NPS - Land Acquisitions - Matching Funds, 1966-1969 (Box 52)
  - USG Dept. of the Interior - NPS - Land Acquisitions - Matching Funds, 1961-1965 (Box 52)
  - USG Dept. of the Interior - NPS - Land Acquisitions - Matching Funds, 1956-1960 (Box 52)
  - USG Dept. of the Interior - NPS - Land Acquisitions - Matching Funds - Printed Material (Box 52)
  - USG Dept. of the Interior - NPS - Lincoln Place Reconstruction - Ford's Theater (Box 52)
  - USG Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service - Virgin Islands National Park - Jetport, 1969-1971 (Box 52)
  - USG Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service - Virgin Islands National Park - Jetport, 1968 (Box 52)
  - Virgin Islands National Park - Virgin Islands Jetport (Proposed) (Box 52)
  - USG Dept. of the Interior - NPS - Virgin Islands National Park (Box 52)
  - Vermont (Box 52)
  - Study of Caneel Bay Plantation Inc. - St. John Virgin Islands, USA (Box 53)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation Inc. - Board of Directors (Box 53)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation Inc. - General Correspondence (Box 53)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation Inc. - Finances (Box 53)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation Inc. - Finances/Audits (Box 53)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation Inc. - Loans (By JHPI) (Box 53)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation Inc. - Low Income Housing (Box 53)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation Inc. - Maps (Box 53)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation Inc. - Memoranda (Box 53)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation Inc. - Meetings (Box 53)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation Inc. - National Park Service (Box 53)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation Inc. - Printed Material/Clippings/Articles (Box 53)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation Inc. - Properties (Box 53)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation Inc. - JHPI - Stock Subscription to Caneel Bay Plantation (Box 53)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation Inc. - Taxes (Box 53)
  - Evaluation of the Historical and Present Position of Grand Teton Lodge Company and Caneel Bay Plantation Inc., 1978 (Box 54)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Art Collection (Box 54)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - General Correspondence (Box 54)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Articles, Clippings, Printed Material (Box 54)
  - Incorporation (Box 54)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Board of Trustees (Box 54)
  - Preliminary Survey of Yellowstone Park Company (Box 54)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Concessions (Box 54)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Finances/Audits (Box 54)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Lillie, Raymond C. (Box 54)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Loans (By JHPI) (Box 54)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Meetings, 1968-1971 (Box 54)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Meetings, 1965-1967 (Box 54)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Wilson-Moore Highway and Route 89 (Box 54)
  - A-M (Box 55)
  - "The Early Days in Jackson Hole", Huidekoper, Virginia (Box 55)
  - National Elk Refuge (Box 55)
  - N-Z (Box 55)
  - A-M (Box 55)
  - N-Z (Box 55)
  - Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia (Box 55)
  - Albright, Horace M. (Box 55)
  - Annual Reports (Box 55)
  - Applicants (Box 55)
  - Applicants (Box 55)
  - Board of Trustees (Box 55)
  - Board of Trustees (Box 55)
  - Brochure/ Booklet (Box 55)
  - Brochure (Box 55)
  - Brochure (Box 55)
  - By Laws (Box 55)
  - Capital Grant Request (Box 56)
  - Cornell University - Laboratory of Ornithology (Box 56)
  - Couch-Sa-Chra-Ga Association, Inc. (Box 56)
  - Clippings (Box 56)
  - College of the Virgin Islands - Caribbean Research Institute (Box 56)
  - Concessions (Box 56)
  - Concessions (Box 56)
  - Conservation Book - "Heritage of Every American" (Box 56)
  - Contributions (Box 56)
  - Eastern National Park and Monument Association (Box 56)
  - Finances (Box 56)
  - Finances (Box 56)
  - Finances/Audits (Box 56)
  - Finances/Audits (Box 56)
  - Finances/Gifts (Box 56)
  - Finances/Gifts to JHPI (Box 56)
  - Finances/Loans (Box 56)
  - Grand Teton Natural History Association (Box 56)
  - Harlem River (Box 56)
  - Harlem River (Box 56)
  - Hudson River Film Company (Box 56)
  - Museum of Indian Arts Dedication, 1972 June 28 (Box 56)
  - Indian Art Collection - US Dept of the Interior (Box 56)
  - Indian Arts Museum, Colter Bay, GTNP - Printed Matter (Box 56)
  - Grand Teton National Park - Indian Arts Museum, Colter Bay (Box 56)
  - Indian Arts Museum, Colter Bay - Printed Material (Box 56)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve - Insurance (Box 56)
  - Jackson Hole Land Use (Box 57)
  - Jackson Hole Land Use (Box 57)
  - Jackson Hole Land Use - Printed Material (Box 57)